In this place,
life and death coexist.
They stand side by side.
Time is no different.
Here, both past and future
are all woven together.
Is this Heaven?
You there.
Hey, you.
Where do you think this is?
This place is...
Otherworld.
That's right. I died.
I failed to exact revenge
against my sworn enemy
and died.
END OF THE 16TH CENTURY, ELSINORE
Father!
Scarlet!
Mother! Father is back!
Father!
- Scarlet!
- I missed you!
Our safe return was assured
thanks to your prayers.
Deploy your troops, Amleth.
Claudius...
It's them or us.
Calm yourself, Brother.
War benefits neither side.
We shall seek balance through negotiation,
building trust, not hostility.
That is our only path to survival.
You are a fool!
Our King Amleth is a good ruler.
Adored by his people
and trusted by neighboring countries.
-
Scarlet. What is important?
Friendship over enmity!
I'll be the princess you want me to be!
Before a princess, you are a young girl.
You must grow up without fear.
- Finished!
- Huh?
I look so handsome. I'm glad.
Uh...
Mother, I'm going to be--
What filthy hands.
My husband loves his daughter...
He is a coward
wearing the guise of virtue.
My husband has everything,
and you have nothing.
Are you not brothers?
Indeed.
I have long dreamed
of pouring poison into his ears.
I will not let him make a mockery of me.
Mark my words.
I belong to the one who will be king.
If your resolve to be king is true,
show me.
Grave news!
Traitors in the castle!
Capture them! They must not escape!
Mark me well! Do not let them get away!
Whoa, there.
Up you go.
Amleth, my brother.
To conspire with a neighboring nation
and betray your country.
Brother, can you not see?
Your insatiable thirst for power
will turn you into a murderer.
Silence!
Loyal subjects!
The traitor must be punished!
Only then,
by God's will, shall I be the new king!
The king would never betray us!
This is a mistake!
Execute him!
Father!
Scarlet!
This cannot be!
What did you say?
What?! What did you say?!
Wait!
Father!
May God bless the new king.
Glory to our King Claudius!
May glory be!
Deploy an army and quell their rebellion.
Hurry up. Move it!
Supposedly, these measures
are to stop the rebellion,
but they torture people
who have nothing to do with it.
"A message for the princess."
"Your subjects are dying of starvation."
"Yet the king will not send aid."
Princess, why not cease your studies
abroad in Wittenberg
and delight our eyes with your beauty?
Princess.
Did you not consider
the possibility of being poisoned?
As naive as an infant.
You'll pay!
Mark my words!
Princess? It can't be!
- Princess?
- What should we do?
Princess!
If this is the afterlife,
will I be reunited with Father?
You will not.
Who are you?
Your father has
already become nothingness.
Nothingness?
You will share his fate,
if you're weak.
My life was one of nothing but regret.
I want to disappear this instant.
I lived a meaningless life.
Uncle Claudius lives,
and Father will not be avenged.
Wait.
That man is here.
What?
He has not become nothingness.
He is somewhere, laughing.
I swear...
I will find him
and avenge my father!
How very foolish humans are.
You bear the crest of Helsingør.
Where is Claudius?
Don't kill me!
- Where is he?!
- I don't want to die!
They are already dead,
yet they still wish to live.
Please. Please wait!
We are allies, Your Highness.
What?
You may
rest assured and follow us.
Their will to hate
and kill each other prevails,
even after death.
Is Claudius really here?
So much for allies!
A grubby princess...
...deserves no salvation!
Capture her!
I may now enter Eternity!
She's hellbent on revenge.
Frailty, thy name is woman.
Wh-What was that?!
She's gone? Find her!
Look.
See her brimming with vitality!
As if she were yet in the land
of the living!
So what is it to be human?
What is it to die?
To live?
Ouch...
I can't do this...
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
♪ It fills this heart ♪
♪ Tell me-- ♪
Oh!
Uh...
- You're hurt all over...
- Uh...
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
What happened?
- Are you a monk?
- I'm a nurse.
- Get thee to a monastery!
- I said I'm a nurse.
You know?
We nurse people back to health.
Yet you're dead?
I'm not dead.
You're wrong.
I'll die someday, sure.
But I even have a pulse.
Then, you wouldn't be here.
And where is "here"?
A whistling arrow.
Was this a battleground?
"Abandon hope,
all ye who enter here."
"The gates of Hell"?
This is Hell? Don't make me laugh.
Disappointed you're not in Heaven?
That's some confidence.
Everybody thinks we go
to Heaven or Hell when we die.
But we all come here without exception.
It's not the afterlife we imagined.
Hold up a sec!
I swear I didn't die.
We received an emergency call...
So, I left the hospital and...
Am I dreaming?
If I'm alive, why am I here?
This must be a mistake!
How did I get here?
I'm a nurse, for crying out loud.
- Why?
- Who knows.
Wait, does that mean you're also dead?
That's right.
- Did you really die?
- Yes.
You don't look it.
Injured, maybe.
Anyways, I'm going home.
I'm still on the clock.
Uh...
Which way do I go?
- What's that?
- Quiet.
Amazing...
Huh?
Hey. Hey!
Wh--
What the...?
Strong...
Cornelius!
Scarlet, daughter of the late King Amleth.
Rumors speak of a mad princess
plotting revenge against King Claudius!
She's the daughter of a king?
I'll never forget your face...
Never!
To continue fighting even after death...
You are a true warrior.
But this ends now.
You will become nothingness.
I must...
...carry out my revenge.
I must have vengeance!
Or I cannot die!
This is the end.
I cannot let him get away with it...
Be that as it may, it is now too late.
Rest in nothingness, Princess.
Damn it.
The bleeding stopped.
No major vessels or nerves were damaged.
Try not to move it.
Where is Claudius?
Answer me!
- In the place closest to Eternity.
- What?
Far away, at the summit
of the magnificent mountains,
is the stairway to Eternity.
Liar!
King Claudius promised to take us,
in exchange for obedience.
My uncle is evil.
This is nonsense!
Yet everyone seeks his salvation
from Otherworld.
People are weak.
I do not know if Eternity even exists,
but I will do anything,
if he will take me there.
Nonsense!
In any world, there are those
that lead and those that follow.
- I won't stand for this!
- What are you doing?
Stop.
I must go.
Here. Use this as a cane.
I'm sorry you got hurt.
Aren't you with the princess?
Don't put too much weight
on your right leg.
You expect me to thank you?
No.
Then stop following me.
You're a fiend.
You'll kill more if I leave you alone.
It's vengeance.
Of course I will.
Still, you shouldn't kill.
I loathe do-gooders like you.
I'm no do-gooder.
My name is Hijiri.
Written with the character
meaning "sacred."
When people are hurt, they bleed.
That's why you need a nurse.
Do as you please.
"At the summit of
the magnificent mountains
is a stairway leading to Eternity."
Bandits!
Run!
Let go!
- Stop it!
- Don't take them!
Stop this!
Can't you see they're elderly?
Stop!
Don't!
They took everything.
Why must we endure
this even after death?
Run!
Gunshots?
W-Wait!
Bandits attacking other bandits?
Oh!
Snap out of it!
Give it here!
That, too!
Wait.
Wait!
Damn it!
- Huh?
- Get down.
-
- Run! Run! Run!
It's coming this way!
What was that?
Are you okay?
Nothingness.
You should feel lucky
you didn't share his fate.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
Look at what's in front of you!
Accept reality, you do-gooder!
I hear it all the time at work.
They say you can't be a nurse
without getting used to death.
That you can't be sad every time.
But if you get used to death,
and your heart grows numb,
you might lose something else.
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
♪ It fills this heart ♪
Why do we humans live?
What's the meaning of life?
Will we ever understand?
Leave those questions to the living.
It's too late for us.
I told you... I'm not dead yet.
The road ahead is treacherous.
- Why not join our caravan.
- Why?
You tried to help us.
We wish to thank you for your kind soul.
Aren't you coming?
They might be bandits.
- They aren't.
- How can you be sure?
Folks, I'm a nurse.
Let me know
if there's anything bothering you.
- Who are you?
- Stay away.
There's no need to. I can help you...
- If you're in pain--
- Forget it.
Who are they? Why did you let them join?
They could be bandits.
Tell them to leave.
You sound like children.
What did I tell you?
The Stairway to Eternity?
I heard people
from different eras and regions
joined forces to protect
the mountain path leading there.
But no one knows
if it's possible to get there.
Just like the world of the living.
I don't think you'll make it that far.
You have to pass through harsh wastelands,
and the bandits.
What's more,
I heard there's a large battalion
blocking the path
leading up to the mountain.
The snake is injured but not dead.
I killed the father,
but the girl yet approaches.
I must not risk turning into nothingness
before my beloved Gertrude arrives.
It feels as though my heart
is filled with scorpions...
Voltemand!
Where are you?
How am I supposed to fight a battalion?
What are you puttin' on him?
It could be poison.
- Stop!
- Don't let him touch you!
Oh... The pain is going away.
How strange! I feel much better.
That's a relief.
You wanna wash my back?
Leave a filthy old man be.
A hot towel is very relaxing.
Waste of a good towel, I tell ya.
Do your wounds hurt?
No...
There are so many.
A scar for every time
we protected the caravan.
Like medals of honor?
You betcha!
That feels so relaxing.
I'm glad.
Even the slightest movement
makes my body hurt.
There's no need to worry.
My hands keep getting duller.
Be conscious of your movement
and your senses won't dull.
Mind if I go next?
- Me, too.
What trickery is this?
No tricks.
All I did was listen to them.
I see you differently.
- Huh?
- But only a little.
♪ Wind-wrought pattern
Rippled on the sand ♪
♪ It reminds me of the ocean
In my hometown ♪
Here you are.
Let's give it a try.
♪ Holding a shell on my cheek
It brings me a nostalgic voice ♪
Ah.
I don't blame you for not trusting others.
We were like you in the beginning.
But the more you're beaten,
robbed, and betrayed,
the more you long for someone to trust.
It's precisely because the world
is such an awful place
that one yearns
for something to believe in.
You must have some deep regret
to have fallen here at such a young age.
♪ We will dance the dance of joy
Till the dawn of night ♪
♪ We will sing a precious song ♪
♪ To the end of the world ♪
- ♪ We will dance forever ♪
- Oh...
♪ Like twisting our fingers
In the blowing wind ♪
♪ We will sing forever ♪
♪ Like we hold hands deep in our hearts ♪
♪ Give us life ♪
♪ So that we can swim wherever we want ♪
♪ Give us life
So that we can fill our empty hearts ♪
Terrible.
- Never seen worse.
- You call that a dance?
- It's bad.
- Never seen worse.
Oh...
♪ We will dance the dance of joy ♪
♪ Till the dawn of night ♪
♪ We will sing a precious song
To the end of the world ♪
♪ We will dance forever ♪
♪ Like twisting our fingers
In the blowing wind ♪
Human words mean nothing to God.
So we send our feelings through dance.
♪ Give us life ♪
♪ So that we can fill our empty hearts ♪
♪ Live! Be well! Thrive! ♪
We will unload at the town ahead.
Your destination lies that way.
You've been so kind.
I pray that you fulfill your wishes.
Thank you very much.
- Oh.
- Be sure to practice.
The old folks talked about it.
At this "Eternity" place
is the most beautiful ocean
you've ever seen!
Ocean?
They said it with a giant smile.
I would love to grow old like them.
What was that?
No!
Going to fight again?
I must have my revenge.
I will do more than knock him out.
There's a Chinese fable
about the ultimate archer.
Huh?
He fires invisible arrows
from an invisible bow.
How about you quit dreaming?
I want you to stop.
There are no wars in the future?
- I'm afraid there are.
- There's your answer.
But at the same time, most of us wish
that the world could escape the violence.
If it doesn't stop somewhere,
the fighting will go on forever.
Are you saying we're at fault
for the wars in your era?
That's not it. But...
Uh...
What are you...?
Hup!
Wait!
Hm?
- Commander Voltemand.
- What?
An emissary?
Waving his arms to surrender?
Makes things quick.
Stop fighting!
What?!
We can talk. No weapons!
Who the hell are you?
And you call yourself a warrior?
- What's with this guy?
- What a coward!
Cut off his ears and nose!
Stop!
The princess!
Scarlet!
You're getting careless!
Steady! Capture the princess!
Is she a princess or a wild animal?
Damn it!
Voltemand.
You injured a lot of my men.
I'll never forgive you!
Stop this, Scarlet!
Hm?
Run! Now!
- Hide in the holes!
- Bring the horses!
Huh?
That man...
His ceasefire was a ruse
to lower our guard.
How cunning.
And unforgivable.
Scarlet!
Damn it! One more!
What are you doing?
You should've left me!
I don't know.
You should also let me be.
I wonder if I will disappear
into nothingness.
I'm doing everything I can. Don't give up!
I'm cutting your sleeve.
- Stop...
- Move your hand.
It's embarrassing.
This is gonna hurt.
Why did you choose this work?
I saw a nurse working to the bone,
trying to help people.
So I wanted to try it.
You must be crazy.
Can you move your hand?
It doesn't seem like
any nerves were damaged.
But you should take it easy for a while.
I just said to--
Whew...
Huh?!
Forgive me.
- I will not.
- I beg you!
You showed my father no mercy.
Wait. Listen to me.
I didn't kill the king.
- Spare me your lies!
- But it's true.
Because I heard him.
I heard what he whispered.
What he whispered?
What? What did you say?!
He could not be heard!
Not by you, but I was by his side.
I heard him.
My hands froze.
I was sure Cornelius heard it, too.
We could not raise our blades.
I heard nothing!
Aren't you curious?
Kill me now, and you'll never know
the king's final words.
Lies! You're lying to escape your fate!
I swear on my soul as a warrior.
Liar!
Very well.
If you tell me, I shall free you.
I swear on my soul as a warrior.
But tell the truth.
What did he say?
One word.
"Forgive."
"Forgive"?
Why? Why would he say that?
Polonius. You have always been
the father of good news.
I received word that Voltemand failed.
Like Cornelius,
we shall punish him till he breaks
and enlighten him of his incompetence.
He will forget about Eternity.
Laertes and I shall track down
the princess and carve her to pieces.
Then go.
Lord Claudius!
Please lead us there!
Please take us to Eternity!
All those who fight alongside me
shall be welcomed to Eternity
without exception!
Thank you, Lord Claudius!
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
Chosen warriors!
Pledge your loyalty to me!
Do not fear!
Fight!
To Eternity!
"Forgive."
If my father did say that,
what did he mean by "forgive"?
Hm... Perhaps he was pleading,
"Please don't kill me. Please forgive me."
My father never feared death
or begged for forgiveness.
Or he was hiding a terrible sin,
and sought forgiveness.
- That's not like him.
- What do you think?
Maybe he was expressing his shame,
as king to his people.
Mm.
But is that truly so?
If I were your father,
I would be sorry
I couldn't watch you grow up.
"Forgive that I'm a terrible father."
All of these have different meanings.
What was his true intent?
There is another way to look at it.
Just my opinion.
- May I?
- What is it?
"Forgive the man you despise.
Forgive Claudius."
But why? Why?
He murdered my father,
stole our country, our home, everything!
I could never forgive such a heinous man.
I believe he wants you
to forgive such a heinous man.
I could never!
I agree. Not even a saint could.
Then...
But I heard him firsthand,
and cannot help but feel this way.
I felt the king's truth speak to me.
What do you mean, "truth"?
I don't understand. What is it?
Why must I forgive?
Why would my father tell me to forgive
the most unforgivable of men? Why?
Why?
You're setting us free?
Excluding our injured,
we could easily best you.
Voltemand, you wouldn't do such a thing.
You forget already? I tried to shoot you.
Let's go.
What have I been fighting for
all this time?
Forgive.
- Why?
- Forgive.
Forgive!
Forgive...
My only thought
was avenging my father.
And yet...
Forgive.
What are you doing?
Wanna see inside?
- Inside?
- Alexander.
- What?
- Caesar.
- Impossible!
- This one's still fresh.
- Huh?
- Someone you want to know more about.
It couldn't be...
Could it be my father?
- Father!
Father!
There's something I don't understand!
Tell me, Father!
- Tell me!
- Father!
The one
you really want to know about...
Is yourself!
Imagine you were living
a completely different life.
What would it be like?
Walking down the street eating ice cream.
Or chatting at a roadside café.
Or peeking through a shop window, then--
Sorry, but you're talking about
a different world.
I have no idea.
I suppose you pity me.
But I don't share it.
There's nothing I can change.
It's the life I've lived.
Even if you died again
and disappeared for good?
I'm not afraid.
In fact, I would like to disappear
as soon as I avenge my father.
Listen. Here's a popular song
from a faraway future.
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
♪ It fills this heart ♪
♪ Tell me everything about love ♪
♪ My purpose for living ♪
♪ Before I lose my heart ♪
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
♪ It fills this heart ♪
♪ I want to know everything about love ♪
♪ A secret hidden somewhere ♪
♪ Find the key for it ♪
Hijiri!
♪ Many encounters ♪
♪ In this endless flow of time ♪
♪ I will meet you ♪
♪ In our promised time ♪
That's... me!
♪ Everything I see ♪
♪ Is shining brightly ♪
♪ And will be reborn ♪
Another... me!
♪ The wind, rain and rainbow ♪
♪ Turn into song ♪
♪ The world ♪
♪ Is so beautiful ♪
♪ Let the seed of me ♪
♪ Break through ♪
♪ Just as I am ♪
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
♪ It fills this heart ♪
♪ Tell me everything about love ♪
♪ My purpose for living ♪
♪ Before I lose my heart ♪
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
You blacked out all of a sudden.
I saw it...
- The era you live in.
- What?
I traveled through time...
And then...
Hijiri, you danced... so well.
Hm?
That's probably not me.
No. You took the lead.
I was really happy.
If I had been born into a different era,
could I have been a different person?
Could I have avoided resigning myself
to all this suffering and frustration?
Scarlet. Don't cry.
I'm right here.
You don't need to cry anymore.
Hey.
Are you a princess?
No.
You're so pretty, I was sure.
I wish I was born as a princess.
Bet you do, too. Right?
If I were a princess,
there's one thing I'd wanna do.
What's that?
I wanna make a world
where kids like us don't have to die.
Yeah.
Eternity...
This paradise lies above
the summit of the sacred mountains!
Only the strong are fit to enter. Listen!
Allow no others
to trespass upon its shores!
Leave finding the princess to me,
- Guildenstern and...
- To me, Rosencranz!
- We will locate her swiftly...
- And go to Eternity.
Yahoo!
Let us pass through to Eternity!
Take us to the summit!
To the summit!
Remove the wall!
- Leave!
- Or we will shoot!
Go! Eternity is just ahead!
Take down Claudius's knights!
Eternity is not theirs to keep!
Charge!
- Please.
- Don't kill me.
- Do not worry.
- We are merely searching.
Searching? Looking for who?
The princess!
Has anybody seen her?
She has her hair braided back.
- Oh! Like this!
- Stop!
- Her hair is like this!
- It hurts...
- Give her back!
- Shut up!
Whoever gives us the princess goes free!
Heck, come along with us to Eternity!
Those are lies!
I'll never be your slave.
Then crawl around
the land of the dead forever.
Let us search elsewhere.
Huh? Wait.
What's this?
A gold coin from Denmark.
Why would you have such a thing?
You know something about the princess?
I don't know anything!
Do not hide it from me. Speak!
If you do not--
Stop! Don't hurt her!
The princess?
We have found the princess!
Get her up!
Princess...
Princess!
Hurry and run! Go!
We captured the princess!
King Claudius will praise us!
- With this...
- He will take us to Eternity!
Scarlet!
- Who the hell are you?
- Let her go!
Huh?
Can't shoot?
What's stopping you?
Is that a toy?
Perhaps this lad
doesn't know how to use a bow?
Why did you come here?
I...
What is your reason
for being in this place?
I...
I...!
Hijiri!
Are you all right?
I'm okay. You?
I'm fine.
You have to live.
I will.
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
♪ It fills this heart ♪
♪ I want to know everything about love ♪
♪ My purpose for living ♪
♪ Before I lose my heart ♪
♪ Tell me about love ♪
♪ It's a miracle everyone knows about ♪
♪ It fills this heart ♪
♪ I want to know everything about love ♪
♪ A secret hidden somewhere ♪
♪ Unravel it for me ♪
- Defeat Claudius!
- Head to the castle!
- He's not here.
- Where is he?
- Did he run away?
- Damn it!
It's already light out again.
Sorry.
This is the summit.
But... There's no Stairway to Eternity!
It's not here.
I thought my uncle would be here.
- He is not here.
- What?
He has already ascended to Eternity.
And you will become nothingness
in the land of the dead.
- Scarlet!
- Hey, now!
Death by fall or death by sword.
The choice is yours.
You?!
Cornelius!
Do we have a rat?
We punished you thoroughly
and took your weapons,
yet you still stand?!
Traitor!
There will be no mercy this time,
only bullets!
Voltemand!
You traitorous dogs!
Why side with the princess?!
We're done being your dogs.
And done with you.
Some cripple with a cane
could never beat me!
Vanish into nothingness!
Damn you!
Move, Voltemand!
Cornelius! Turn into nothingness!
Your target is up there.
You have made it this far.
Go have your revenge.
Thank you.
Is that...?
O great gate!
Door to Eternity!
I am the king!
Claudius!
Yet why do you shut your door?!
Why? Why?
Curses!
I've come this far. What am I missing?
These bloody hands...
My sins. O, my offense is rank...
There is nothing else now
but to pray for salvation.
Or is it too late for such things?
And how?
I still hold the spoils of my sins.
The crown, the ambition, and the queen...
How may one be pardoned?
Penitence...
It's the only way. I must repent.
Forgive me, a man of many sins.
Save me.
I toiled my utmost
for countless unhappy people
who seek Eternity.
So please save me...
King Claudius,
I understand your true intentions.
However,
I must ask one thing of you.
Please, admit that you were wrong.
That killing my father was a mistake.
Ask for his daughter's forgiveness.
Uncle.
Ask for forgiveness?
What a joke!
I have only one regret now.
That I didn't torture your father more
before killing him,
so that you may tremble in fear
and never defy me!
I should have drained his blood,
and stripped the meat from his bones
as he begged me
for the sweet release of death.
Had I made you watch that,
you would not come before me now
with your ridiculous, foolish words!
And what of your penitence just now,
or your toil for the people?
What benefit is there
in bringing others with me?
- Eternity belongs to me!
Mine and mine alone!
How is it that a man whose wretched heart
overflowing with greed stands here?
You trample upon the hopes of others.
How can you possibly enter Eternity?
Shall I have you feel
just a fraction of the pain and regret
my father did because of you?
Shall I show you?
Forgive.
Should I follow through
with my revenge?
Or should I forgive all?
Why must I suffer so?
What is that binds me?
I don't know!
Can I not find a different way to live?
I don't know! I don't know! I don't know!
Then I am hopeless.
I can't help it!
This is how I've lived for so long!
True. Then, I am hopeless,
and this is the end.
Hatred drove me to learn swordsmanship.
For vengeance, for my father,
and all who suffer.
I have held myself back,
over and over again.
I told myself,
"This is not how things should be."
Until now, I have lived my life
without forgiving myself,
without forgiving myself...
without forgiving myself.
Myself.
Forgive.
Myself...
Scarlet.
Father!
Stop this foolishness
of carrying out vengeance in my name.
There must be another "you"
that you long for,
that is not consumed
by hatred and vengeance.
I want you to live your life
and treasure it.
I want to see you shine, living freely.
Father.
Listen well.
This is not a place for a girl like you,
the daughter of a failure!
Eternity belongs to me.
No one else may enter.
Only me and my queen
shall pass through this gate!
Descend into nothingness!
Follow your wretched father!
I do not forgive you.
I cannot forgive you. However...
I am done fighting.
For the sake of all who have wished
for an end to the conflict.
It means there's a chance
for people in the future
to live together in peace.
Wrap your empty ideals
in pretty words, you fool!
You shall disappear without a trace!
Gertrude!
Please! Help me!
Eternity is...
Gertrude!
Eternity is right in front of us...
I don't want to disappear!
Don't let me become nothingness!
Help me!
Gertrude!
Save me! I don't want to die!
I don't want to die!
Finally...
I've finally seen things
through to the end.
I can disappear in peace now.
You're wrong about that, Scarlet.
What?
Humans still
call this place Otherworld,
Eternity and so on.
But they are sorely mistaken.
This is a world where life and death
are in coexistence, not conflict.
Not only life and death, but time as well.
Here, the past and future blur together.
That is why you are together.
Now,
there is one among you two who yet lives.
Not dead?
The time for the living to awaken
is fast approaching.
That individual cannot be here.
The time has nearly come to return
to the place from whence they came.
Yes. You mean him.
He's said from the beginning,
that he's not dead.
That he came here by some mistake. So...
You're wrong. It's not me.
What?
It's you, Scarlet.
It's come back to me. I really did die.
ER headquarters
to all ambulances.
Ambulances have been sent out.
Two men have been found unconscious.
That's all from ER headquarters.
Urgent. Urgent.
ER headquarters to all departments.
Suspected knife attack.
-
The suspect has not been apprehended.
Be alert for the suspect's movements.
I didn't plan on dying.
I just acted on instinct
and jumped in between.
That's why I didn't realize
that I was dead.
I kept believing I was alive.
I'm dead. You're the one who's alive.
It isn't me.
It couldn't be me!
The blade reached my organs.
I stopped the bleeding for a while,
but it started again.
No...
You're wrong! It's not me!
Hijiri! You have to live!
Then I'll stay here! I'll stay with you!
Oh, God...
Bring Hijiri back to life, not me!
No.
Please! He can take my place!
I shouldn't be the one to live.
I was the one
who was obsessed with revenge.
No.
- You need to live, Scarlet.
- I don't want to.
Live. Say clearly that you want to live.
No!
Say you want to live!
No! It means parting with you, Hijiri!
It's fine that way! You need to live!
- I don't want to be apart!
- Say you want to live!
Put it into words!
"I want to live! I want to live!"
I... want to... live.
More! "I want to live!"
I want to live!
- More!
- I want to live! I want to live!
I want to live!
I'll live, and in exchange,
by the time you're born,
I'm going to make it
a world with less conflict.
If the future changes,
surely you won't be killed, right?
For that, I'll do everything that I can!
Then you can live longer, too, Hijiri!
You can have a family, raise kids,
and grow into a fine old man!
What is it...
to be human?
What is it to die?
To live?
And...
what is love?
Your Highness?
The princess!
The princess has come back to us!
- To be sure!
- The antidote worked!
It's a miracle!
It happened
while you lay in your coma.
He drank from a cup
intended for the one he was to slay.
And then...
His was a sudden end.
Why are you still alive?
Why is my husband dead,
yet you are here and not in Hell?
Why?!
Surely you wanted to exact revenge
with your own hands.
No, all is done.
Pardon?
Finally,
my journey has come to an end.
May God bless the new queen.
Glory to our new queen!
May glory be!
- Our new queen!
- Yes?
Can you promise not to oppress us
like the previous king?
I'm tired of the poor always
being the fool.
That's right!
My people!
If you will have me
as the leader of this country,
I will serve for the sake
of happiness for all.
Friendship and trust with our neighbors.
Not hostility.
Preventing the deaths of children.
Even if I must endure suffering and pain,
I pledge never to give up until I find
a path forward without conflict.
For all who have died
wishing for an end to war.
And for all who are yet to be born
wishing for happiness.
Can there... really be a world
without war in the future?
Yes.
With your help, there can be.
Then, we'll also believe in you
and never give up.
- Me too!
- I support you.
- We will!
Glory to our new leader!
May glory be!